Thank you guys
for having us over.
Yeah, this is fun.
Couples night.
Yeah, I don't know why
we don't hang out
with married couples
more often.
Well, because every time we do,
you make jokes about swinging
and scare them away.
You mean
that Portuguese couple?
Yeah, like you wouldn't
have done it.
Hey, you guys,
I have great news.
Ross, we're kind of
in the middle of dinner here.
Oh, well, uh, I already ate,
but sure.
Guess what happened
at work today.
A dinosaur died
a million years ago?
Uh, try 65 million
years ago,
and then try shh!
My, uh, tenure review board
met today,
and I hear it's looking
really good.
Wow.
That's great.
Do you have any idea
what this means
in academic circles, huh?
I am going to get laid.
Hi, you guys.
Hey.
Ooh, Italian.
Uh, no one... no one
wanted seconds, right?
No, I'm-I'm good.
Hey, you guys,
you're never going
to believe it.
This headhunter called me.
I have a meeting tomorrow
with Gucci.
Gucci wants me.
I'm up for tenure.
Congratulations.
You too. What
are the odds?
Oh...
Guess what?!
I finally got that seed
out of my teeth!
I don't know
who I'm happiest for.
I do. He's been working
on that all day!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, Mon, was it weird changing
your name to Geller-Bing?
No. No, it felt nice
to acknowledge this.
Where did you go to do it?
Um, the, uh...
the-the Ministry of Names...
Bureau.
You never did it!
I'm sorry. It's just the idea
of-of being an official Bing...
Hey, I will have
you know that...
Aw, who am I kidding?
Let's call the kid Geller
and let Bing die with me.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Honey, would you want
me to take your name?
Oh, it's up to you.
It's your name.
You've got to live with it.
All right, let's see.
Call me "Mrs. Hannigan."
Mrs. Hannigan?
What?! Can't you see
I'm in the middle of something?!
Ooh, I like it.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Joe.
We got a couple things
we got to check out
at the new house.
You want to come
with us?
No, thank you.
Joey, I know you're not happy
about us moving,
but you're the only one
who hasn't seen the house.
Yeah, come with us.
You'll see how close
it is to the city.
But, no, it's not close.
You said it was in Escrow.
I couldn't even find that
on the map.
Joey, please come.
It would mean so much to us.
You know what?
You are my friends.
I want to be supportive.
I will come with you. Shotgun.
Damn it!
All right,
see you guys later.
Okay.
We'll pick you up
at 11:00.
I'm so glad
you're coming.
Good for you. That
was really mature.
No. The only reason I'm going
to their stupid new house
is so I can point out
everything that's wrong with it
so they don't move.
I'm going to make 'em stay here!
You're a strange kind
of grownup.
Joey, you can't make
someone do something
they don't want to do.
Believe me,
there's something
I've been trying
to get Mike to do in
bed, and there's...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
Could we not talk
about that now?
All right, prude.
Look, Monica and
Chandler really
love this house.
You are not going
to talk them into
staying here.
Hey, hey, I can
convince people
to do anything.
You know, I bet you
I could even get Mike
to do that thing.
What is it?
I am not going to help you
do that!
Oh, my... God!
Hi, um, I'm here to see
Mr. Campbell with Gucci.
The reservation's
probably under Gucci.
It's-it's spelled like "Gucky,"
which can be confusing.
Mr. Campbell's not here yet.
Let me show you
to his table.
Oh, my God,
that's my boss!
You have to seat us
somewhere else.
I'm sorry, that's always
Mr. Campbell's table.
No, but my... but my boss
cannot see me.
I'm interviewing
for another job.
I know... with "Gucky."
Shh!
Rachel?
Hi, I'm on a date!
That's... great.
Yeah, it is, yeah.
You know, it's tough.
Single mom, career.
You got to get out there!
Well... you've got
a good energy.
Oh...
Rachel?
Yes, hi.
James Campbell.
Hi.
Excuse us.
Please.
Okay. Oh...
Well, now, he's cute.
So... your resume
is quite impressive.
My... my resume?
I wouldn't... I wouldn't call
my-my online dating profile
a resume.
Dating profile?
No, no, I'm...
I'm talking about
the work resume...
♪ La, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la... ♪
Whatever happened to just
singing for no reason?
Maybe people found it weird.
So...
why do you want to leave
Ralph Lauren?
What?! I-I-I don't.
You don't?
No, I-I love...
I love it there!
If you don't want to leave,
why are we having this lunch?
( whispering ):
That is my boss.
What?
That's Hugo Boss?
No...
God, this place
is so depressing.
If I had to work here,
I'd kill myself.
But you obviously haven't.
How can I help you?
Um, I need to change
my name, please.
See, I need to change it, 'cause
I'm-I'm hiding from the law.
You're fun.
You need to fill
out this form.
Okay, well, just so I know-- I
don't know how it works exactly.
See, my name is, um, Buffay, and
my husband's name is Hannigan,
so is it supposed to be
Buffay-Hannigan or
Hannigan-Buffay?
It can be
anything you want.
Well, not anything.
Yeah. Anything.
Oh, this could take a while.
Get out of my line.
Okay.
Hey.
Hey, Pheebs.
Ooh, not anymore.
I changed it today.
Oh, I'm sorry,
"Mrs. Hannigan."
Wrong again.
Apparently, you can change it
to anything you want,
so I thought, all right,
here's an opportunity
to be creative...
so, meet...
Princess Consuela Bananahammock.
That's what we were
going to name the baby.
Phoebe...
Uh, Princess Consuela.
You seriously changed
your name to that?
Uh-huh.
Okay, so from now on,
we have to call you
Princess Consuela?
Um, no, I-I'm going to have
my friends call me Valerie.
Hey, how'd the
interview go?
Oh... not good.
You know, I always feel that way
after an interview.
I'll bet it went better
than you think.
Well, I didn't get
the job at Gucci, and I got
fired from Ralph Lauren.
That is a bad interview.
What are you...? Well, what
are you talking about?
How'd this happen?
Well, my boss
was at the same restaurant
where I was having my interview,
and he heard everything,
so later,
he calls me into his
office and he tells me
that he's going
to have to let me go
because I'm not a team player,
and I say, "Wait a minute.
No, yes, I am,"
and then I had to sit there
for 45 minutes
while he proved that that,
in fact... was true.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
( sighs )
Hey.
What? Ooh, wh-what's this?
Why, it's... it's a bottle
of champagne.
Well, why is this here?
Ross...
I guess it's here because...
I got tenure!
Wow.
Congratulations.
This is the single greatest day
of my professional career.
Gunther, six glasses!
Six?
You-you want me to join you?
Oh, I thought Joey was here.
Five is good.
Wow, I'm going to have a loogie
in my coffee tomorrow.
Ooh, Israeli champagne...
and it's vanilla.
I got tenure.
I didn't win the lottery.
Hey, Rach, so, uh,
how did your thing go?
Oh, it went good, yeah,
but I'm not going to hear
about that for a couple
of days.
Oh, you know what?
You're going to get it.
I-I-I-I can feel it.
Can you?
Well, everybody,
here's to Ross.
And-and to years of hard
work finally paying off.
And to knowing that your career
doesn't mean everything.
But also knowing it means
a lot.
But more importantly,
to full,
well-rounded lives.
That center around work.
To Ross!
You know what the best
part about this is?
I can never be fired.
Oh, God...
No, seriously.
I have job
security for life.
You know, I mean, I
never have to worry.
Oh, oh, look at you.
Look how happy
you are for me.
( sniffles ):
No, it's not that.
I got fired today...
and I didn't get
the other job.
Oh, my God.
Rach, I'm so sorry.
Oh...
Great. I feel
like an idiot.
No, it's okay.
You didn't know.
Oh...
A little heads-up
would've been nice.
Thank you for letting
us see the house again.
And thank you for explaining
to us what escrow means.
I've already forgotten
what you said, but thank you.
Take as long
as you want.
Just let me know
when you're through.
Oh, I'm so glad
you decided to come.
Me, too.
Yeah, this place
is great.
I'm so happy
for you guys.
Although, you know,
I hope you like fungus.
What?
Fungus.
Yeah, the place is full of it.
No, it's not.
We had an inspection
and they didn't
find anything.
Okay, then I guess
I have dry eyes
and a scratchy throat
for no reason.
Maybe it's because
you hung your head
out of the window like
a dog the whole ride here.
Maybe.
So this is the, uh,
living room, huh?
Ooh, it's
pretty dark.
No, it's not.
Are you kidding?
I think I just saw
a bat in the corner.
When your head was
hanging out the window,
it didn't hit
a mailbox, did it?
Maybe.
I just
think you guys
could do better than
this house, you know?
Or any other house,
for that matter.
Oh, Joey, look.
We know you're having
a hard time with this,
but we really,
we love it here.
Fine, okay, if you
love this house so much,
then you should
just live here, okay?
I just hope you get used
to that weird humming sound.
( humming )
Joey, we know
that's you.
Nope... it's not.
( humming )
Hey.
Welcome back.
Oh, I missed you.
Oh, me, too.
So what's new?
Well, I'm no longer
Phoebe Buffay.
That's great.
You changed
your name?
Yes, I did.
Meet Princess Consuela
Bananahammock.
You're kidding, right?
Nope.
You really did that?
Yup.
You can't
do that.
Why? Why?
It's fun, it's different
and no one else has
a name like it.
All right, then I'm
going to change my name.
Great, okay.
What are you going
to change it to?
Crap Bag.
Mike Crapbag?
No. No Mike.
No, just Crap Bag.
First name Crap.
Last name Bag.
You're not serious, right?
Yeah,
I'm serious.
It's fun, it's different,
and no one else has
a name like that.
Well, then great!
If you love it, I love it.
I do love it.
And I love your name.
I love Princess Consuela.
And I love Crap.
( groans )
Who are you?
Oh, hi. I'm Joey.
My stupid friends
are buying this house.
Who are you?
I'm MacKenzie.
My stupid parents
are selling this house.
Oh...
I hate my parents.
I hate my friends.
All right, look.
There's got to be a way
that we can stop
this from happening.
Like what?
Uh...
Ooh! Okay.
You come with me
and you tell them
that the house is haunted.
What are you, eight?
Oh, ooh, okay.
Let's hear your great idea.
I don't have any great ideas.
I am eight.
( grumbles )
There's got to be a way.
I mean, if Monica
and Chandler move out here,
and now Phoebe's
married to Mike,
that just leaves me
and Ross and Rach.
You know what I mean?
I really don't.
What am I going to do?
I feel like
I'm losing my friends.
My parents say I'm going
to make new friends.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Easy for you. You're young.
Me, I'm set in my ways.
This is what my mom
was talking about.
Whiners are wieners.
Look, you want your friends
to be happy, right?
Yeah, yeah, I guess. Yeah.
Well, if moving here
is going to make them happy,
don't you want them to do it?
Yeah. Maybe.
Then you got to let them go.
( grumbles )
I hate to admit it,
but you're...
you're probably right.
How'd you get to be so smart?
I read a lot.
Just when I thought
we could be friends.
Oh, hey, Rach.
I just heard.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, thank you...
You still don't know
my name, do you?
Well, now I don't have to.
Ross, what is taking
you so long?
I'm sorry.
It's almost as if
this wasn't built
for a quick getaway.
Rachel?
Mark?
Oh, my God.
How have you been?
Fantastic.
You remember Ross.
Sure, sure.
What's with
the chair?
Uh, you know,
you can't always get
a seat on the subway, so...
Clever.
So, how are you?
Well, you're not catching
me on my best day.
Yeah, a box full
of your desk stuff
doesn't exactly
say "big promotion."
No, but it's good.
You know, I'm going
to take some time off
and...
some charity work.
Are you sure, because
we may have something
at Louis Vuitton.
Well, screw charity work.
What do you got?
Why don't we have dinner tonight
and talk about it?
Great.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Nice to see you again.
Yeah, yeah. I got tenure.
Oh, my God!
See, I told you
something good would come along.
And he seemed really nice.
I've met him before?
Ross, that's Mark.
From Bloomingdale's?
You were insanely
jealous of him.
That is Mark?!
Yes.
I hate that guy!
No, no,
no, no.
You cannot
go to dinner with him.
What? You don't
want me to get a job?
Oh, yeah, I'm sure he's
going to give you a job.
Maybe make you his sex-retary.
I'm serious.
I just don't trust
that guy, okay?
Ross, you know what?
Okay, let's
talk about it later.
There comes security.
Oh, I love
this street.
The trees and the
big front yards,
and the actual
picket fences.
Man, those two dogs are going
at it.
Hey.
Hey, where
you been?
Oh, just, uh,
you know, looking around.
But you know what?
This house is great.
Really?
What changed your mind?
Oh, well, the little girl
who lives here made me feel
a lot better
about the whole thing.
Joey, there was a little girl
who lived here,
but she died,
like, 30 years ago.
What?
Ha! I'm just messing with you.
That's not funny.
You know I'm afraid
of little girl ghosts.
Joey, now that
you're okay
with the house,
do you want to go
see your room?
What?
I get my own room?
You don't think
we'd buy a house
and not have a Joey room,
do you?
Oh, my God.
CHANDLER:
Hey.
Oh, oh.
Hey, can I have an aquarium?
And a sex swing?
No.
Why not?
I'll keep the tank clean.
After you, Ms.
Bananahammock.
Thank you, Mr. Bag.
Hmm.
Oh, hey.
Oh, hi, Rita!
How are you?
Good.
Oh, Rita's a massage client.
Yeah.
Oh.
Why don't you introduce me?
Uh, Rita, this
is my husband.
Oh.
Yeah.
Why don't you tell her
my name?
( laughs )
Okay, I will.
This is, um...
This is my
husband, um,
Crap Bag.
Crap Bag?
If you need an easy way
to remember it,
just think of a bag of crap.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Oh. Okay, fine.
You made your point.
Can you please just be
Mike Hannigan again?
Only if you'll be Phoebe Buffay.
How about, um...?
How about Buffay-Hannigan?
Really?
Yeah.
I'm Phoebe Buffay-Hannigan
Bananahammock.
Do you even know
what a bananahammock is?
It's a funny word?
It's a Speedo.
Oh, crap.
Hey, is Rachel here?
MONICA:
Hey. No.
She's still at dinner?
I guess.
Why, who's she with?
That guy Mark.
From Bloomingdale's?
She thinks
he's just being nice to her.
But I know he really wants
to sleep with her.
It's seven years ago.
My time machine works!
We ran into him
on the street today,
and he said
he might have a job for her,
but I know he just wants
to get into her pants.
So what if he wants
to sleep with her?
I mean,
she's single, and he's cute.
Excuse me?
Oh, please.
Yesterday on the subway,
you couldn't stop staring
at that woman
with the big breasts
the whole time.
For your information,
I was staring at her baby.
We're about to be parents.
Oh. Sorry.
Hi, you guys.
Hi. So, uh...
Hi.
how was dinner?
Oh, it was great.
Mark is so sweet.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. I wonder why.
What could that smarmy
letch possibly want?
Oh, Ross.
Come on.
He is happily married.
His wife just had twins.
Should we send something?
How did the
job stuff go?
He offered me one.
That's great.
Oh, my God!
Congratulations.
I know. It's amazing.
It's amazing.
It's so much better
than what I had at Ralph Lauren.
The money is great.
Can we... Can we just
stop for a second?
Who said something better
would come along, huh?
You didn't
believe me.
I told you everything
was going to work out.
( gasps )
You know what?
This calls for a bottle
of Israel's finest!
The job is in Paris.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
I mean, the soap opera's
a great gig,
but am I missing opportunities?
You know, I've always thought
of myself as a serious actor.
I mean, should I be trying
to do more independent movies?
I don't know.
But you know what?
I'm going to put you
on with my bear.
Hold on.
Hey, bear,
I need some career advice.